mynexia.com 2010-07-10

# Privacy Policy | businessboard

## businessboard Privacy Policy Highlights

This page summarizes the key highlights from our privacy policy.

### 1\. Personal Information

We collect information:

  1. When you post bulletins and register an account to become a businessboard member, We use cookies and other technologies to recognize you, customize your experience and serve advertisements.
  2. We automatically receive from your internet use such information as your IP address, the URL’s of sites from which you link to or leave our website, your type of browser and ISP.

### 2\. Uses Of Personal Information

We use the information you provide to:

  * Post bulletins and administer your account with us.
  * Send you service or promotional communications through email and notices on this website.
  * Enable you to share your information and communicate with other users, or provide your personal details to third parties offering combined services with businessboard.

We will never sell, rent or otherwise provide your personal identifiable information to any third parties for marketing purposes. In order to deliver our services, we may share information with third parties, such as the credit card processing company we use, to process subscription payments made by you.

### 3\. Your Information Entitlements

You can:

  * Create, review, enhance or edit your information and bulletins
  * Choose what information you make available

### 4\. Important Information

  * Notice of all changes that materially affect ways in which your personal information may be used or shared will be posted in updates to our Privacy Policy.

### 5\. Security

  * Personal information you provide will be secured with industry standards and technology.

### 6\. How To Contact Us

  * If you have any questions or comments please email us at [privacy@businessboard.com](mailto:privacy@businessboard.com)

________________________________________

## Businessboard Privacy Policy

Your privacy is our top concern. We work hard to earn and keep your trust, so we adhere to the following principles to protect your privacy:

  * We will never rent or sell your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes.
  * We will never share your contact information with another user without your consent.
  * Any personally identifiable information that you provide will be secured with all industry standard protocols and technology.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. If you continue to use the businessboard service after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on our site, you hereby provide your consent to the changed practices.

Please read this privacy policy to learn more about:

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours is collected by businessboard.
  2. How the information is used.
  3. With whom the information may be shared.
  4. How you can access and change your Account information.
  5. What security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information collected by businessboard.
  6. How to contact us. 

________________________________________

### 1\. Personal Information Collected

We collect your personal information in the following ways:

**Registration**

In order to become a businessboard member, you must first create an account on this web site.

**Posting Bulletins**

You will provide basic information when you post bulletins in businessboard.

**Cookies**

Like most web sites, businessboard uses cookies and web log files to track site usage. A cookie is a tiny data file which resides on your computer which allows businessboard to recognize you as a user when you return to our site using the same computer and web browser. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies, you will not be able to use our website. Like the information you enter at registration or in your Profile, cookie and log file data is used to customize your experience on the web site.

**Web Beacons**

We may allow other companies, called ad networks, to serve advertisements. Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms.  
Businessboard never provides personally identifiable information to any advertiser nor any third party.

**Log files, IP addresses and information about your computer**

Due to the communications standards on the Internet, when you visit the businessboard web site we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave businessboard. We also receive the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system and type of web browser you are using, email patterns, as well as the name of your ISP. This information is used to analyze overall trends to help us improve the businessboard service. The linkage between your IP address and your personally identifiable information is never shared with third-parties without your permission or except when required by law.

### 2\. Uses Of Personal Information

The information you choose to provide on this site is used to help you find valuables business matches.

**businessboard Communications**

businessboard will communicate with you through email and notices posted on this website or through any other means available through the service. If we send any communications to you via the carrier service with which you have a mobile communications subscription or otherwise have access, you understand you will pay any service fees associated with any such access

**Sharing Information With Third Parties**

businessboard takes the privacy of our users very seriously. We will never sell, rent, your personally identifiable information to any third parties. We will only share your personally identifiable information with third parties to carry out your instructions and to provide specific services or information. For instance, we use a credit card processing company to bill users for subscription fees. These third parties do not retain, share, or store any personally identifiable information except to provide these services and are bound by strict confidentiality agreements which limit their use of such information.

We may provide aggregated anonymous data about the usage of our services to third-parties for such purposes as we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate, including, without limitation, to prospective advertisers on businessboard. We may segment our users by industry, geographic location, or company.

**Teaming with Other Organizations to Offer Combined and Other Services**

businessboard may offer our services in connection with other web sites (including updates about the businessboard service) or may team with other online services to give you the combined results of both services or additional services and benefits. Platform Applications (as defined in the User Agreement) can be designed by Platform Developers (as defined in the User Agreement) or by a subset of Platform Developers with whom businessboard has more closely aligned (“Partners”).

**Create bulletins**

If you post bulletins in businessboard you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. businessboard is not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

**Legal Disclaimer**

It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on our company or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

**Disclosures to others**

We may also disclose your personal and other information you provide, to another third party as part of a reorganization or a sale of the assets of a businessboard corporation division or company and only after taking steps to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected. Any third party to which we transfer or sell businessboard’s assets will have the right to continue to use the personal and other information that you provide to us.

### 3\. Your Information Choices

**Accessing and Changing Your Account Information**

You can review the personal information you provided us and make any desired changes to the information you publish, or to the settings for your businessboard account at any time by logging in to your account on the businessboard website. We may retain certain data contributed by you if it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally-identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. All retained data will continue to be subject to the terms of the businessboard Privacy Policy in effect at the time of your request.

### 4\. Important Information

**Children**

Children are not eligible to use our service and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us or use the service.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

businessboard may update this privacy policy. In the event there are significant changes in the way we treat your personally identifiable information, we will display a notice on this site. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

If you continue to use the businessboard service after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on our site, you hereby provide your consent to the changed practices.

### 5\. Security

To protect any data you store on our servers we also audit our system for possible vulnerabilities and attacks and we use a tier-one secured-access data center. It is your responsibility to protect the security of your login information.
